I read my journey has had an update
maybe a month ago where they now do
product shots really well okay so
product short of coffee packets
minimalistic black logo brown coffee
packets of a company called Ghost House
Coffee so check this out okay dude this
looks professional as heck you can put
this on a website almost immediately
this gives you such a killer idea of
what your brand will look and feel like
when it's on a product so great mood
board by the way there's something
called chaos and mid Journey did you do
the same thing brown color now dash dash
c space 75 between every generation it
increases the randomness of the Next
Generation so it gives you more varied
outputs all this High chaos okay yeah so
the it's more variable yeah in its
Generations yes
this one's really nice yeah
do this damn book yeah holy that's
so good